[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Red Cross"], "LOCATION": ["Staten Island"], "TIME": ["this morning"]}, "docId": "121101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBD", ":", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 33, "question": "Do you endorse what he said?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 34, "answer": "Well, I think it was a sentiment of frustration this morning because we hadn't had -- seen a real response here in Staten Island, but you know, we had our senators out here today, and I can say that the Red Cross is on the grounds right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "Do people there feel comfortable that this is going ahead?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "ALLIOTAKIS: Absolutely not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 70, "question": "First of all, how is he doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 71, "answer": "He's doing good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "DT", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 76, "question": "Compared to the events and the aftermath of 9/11, how do you view what is happening in Staten Island?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "Right now, we all need help.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Staten Island"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 103, "question": "So you did not see a woman with two children?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 104, "answer": "No, absolutely not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 112, "question": "And what did he do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 113, "answer": "He took a concrete flower pot.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 123, "question": "Well, let me ask you, the man -- if a man threw a flower pot, did you let the man in your house?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 124, "answer": "He didn't ask to come in.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 127, "question": "I couldn't -- what could I do to help him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", ":", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": "All right, so...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "121101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VB", "DT", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "Did you believe him, I suppose, is the obvious question?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "Well, I think it's really important, Piers, is whether I believed him or not, he did acknowledge that there was a man who came by, and the man threw something at his back door and he wasn't willing to help the man.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 166, "question": "What is the reaction of the community there to what's happened there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "TO", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 167, "answer": "Well, our initial reaction was from the police who were on the scene.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 199, "question": "And are you satisfied they're doing all they can to get people back to full power?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "PRP", "MD", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "RB", "TO", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "You know, I'm going to spend time in the postmortem looking at pre-storm preparedness.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}, "docId": "121101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "VB", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBG", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "How are you tonight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "I've got half my staff, never mind anybody else in New York, all homeless, wondering when the hell they're getting their power back.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 370, "question": "What do you say to people who are now heading towards day four with no power and not able to be in their homes or to use water or anything?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", "NN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "TO", "VB", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "Yes, no, it's an extraordinary ordeal that everyone is going through, and we're working very hard to get the power back on as quick as we can.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "NN", ",", "RB", "NN", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "Can you give a guarantee that everybody will be back on a week by Saturday, for instance?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "Well, we're saying that we're going to get almost everybody, virtually everyone back by next weekend.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Saturday"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "CD", "CC", "CD", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "What happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "Well, shortly after 7:30 or 8:00, the power went out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "You stayed there, I believe, until about 3:00 a.m. and then in rushed firemen and other emergency services saying, grab your baby and get out now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "IN", "CD", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "VBG", ",", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VB", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "We need to go now, yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["3:00 a.m."]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "There was a hurricane raging outside?", "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 446, "question": "You were carried down nine floors?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 447, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 458, "question": "But it was scary because you were taken to the wrong hospital first, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "And he is fine?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "He is fine, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 470, "question": "What do you feel about the fact that these back-up generators failed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 471, "answer": "I'm quite upset, actually.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "NNS", "VBP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "Well, first of all, you know, the planet is warmer than it was and people have something to do with it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "You are a firm believer in climate change being responsible for this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "That's right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "NNS", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 579, "question": "On that one point, what do you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 580, "answer": "That we have a very limited data series on hurricanes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 589, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 590, "answer": "I am.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 592, "question": "Were you satisfied with his explanation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 593, "answer": "As consumer, I want that power back immediately.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 599, "question": "So New Yorkers are impatient but do you think they are right to be angry now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNPS", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 600, "answer": "I think that Con-Ed for right now is -- I think they are scrambling.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121101pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 614, "question": "Charles, we'll start with you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 615, "answer": "I don't think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]